Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - Service Table Commutation Columns, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L57.2
  - Electronic Calculator Tests, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L57.3
  - Social Security History, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L58
  - Sound Policy for Social Security- Booklet, 1958 February (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L58.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 13)
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES:, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L60.a
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES:, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L60.b
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L60.c
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES:, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L60.d
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES:, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L60.e
  - CANADIAN INSTITUTE OF ACTUARIES:, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L60.f
  - Kwasha Lipton- Consulting Actuaries, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L60.1
  - Joe Lynch And Co.(Lynch Valuation), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L60.2
  - Layman- Instructions To Punch Card Processing, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L60.2a
  - Edward H. Friend and Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L60.3
  - American Income Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L61
  - Illinois Buisness Review Article by M.W.L.-Need for Regulation of Private Pension Plans, 1967 July (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L62
  - Alexander Hamilton Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L64
  - Papers, undated (Box 14)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L64.1
  - Connecticut General Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L64A
  - Insurance Companies- Financial Data-Cost of Living Wage Clause & Cost of Insurance-Basic Steel, 1961 June (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L64.B
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L64c
  - The Travellers Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L64d
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Ins. Co-Deposit Administration, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L64E
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L64.F
  - Massachusetts General Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L64.G
  - Prudential Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L64 H
  - The Phoenix Companies, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L64 I
  - Nationwide Insurance Company, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L64 J
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L64 K
  - Integration of Social Security And Pension Plans, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L65
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L66
  - National Coordinating Committee-Multi-Employer Plans, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L67
  - FEDERAL COORDINATOR OF TRANSPORTATION: -Advisory Committee on Railroad Employment, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L75.2
  - FEDERAL COORDINATOR OF TRANSPORTATION: -Advisory Comm. on Railroad Employment Proposed Pension Plans, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L75.2a
  - Papers, undated (Box 15)
  - FEDERAL COORDINATOR OF TRANSPORTATION: -Dismissal Compensation, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L75.7
  - FEDERAL COORDINATOR OF TRANSPORTATION: -Material on Transportation Unemployment Compensation Act, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L75.8
  - Variable Annuities, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L76
  - Society of Actuaries, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L77
  - Fort Wayne Conference,United Steel Workers of America, Annual Education Conference,-Ordinary Insurance Purchases, 1967 February (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L78
  - Canadian Pensions, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L79
  - Canada-Provincial Insurance Statutes, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L79.a
  - Full Employment Legislation, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L86
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Proposed Bills, Memos, Reports,Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L87
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Amendment, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L87.a
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Correspondence, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L87.b
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -RR. Unemployment Insurance, A Report by Annette Kornblum, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L87.c
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: - Amendment of 1953. Misc. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L87.d
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: - Amendment of 1953 Testimony before Committee of Labor And Public Welfare (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L87.e
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Amendment of 1953 Hearing Notes for Appendix to M.WL. Statement, 1953 June 02 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L87.E
  - Papers, undated (Box 16)
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Legislation,73rd-77th Congress, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L87.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Lesislation,78th-81st, + 85th Congress, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L87.2
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Hawkins,Everett, D.Rairoad Retirement Systems in The U.S, Capts.1-196(Industrial Relations Counselers Inc. Study, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L88
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -VOLUNTARY Railroad Pension Plans,Retirement Rates, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L89.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -Voluntary Railroad Pension Plans-Data on Annual Earnings and Salery Scales, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L89.2
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -RR Retirement Act, Original Cost Estimates, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L90
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT: -RR Mortality 7 Commutation Columns, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L91
  - Group Rates - hospital, Medical, Surgical, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L92
  - Group Permanent Insurance, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L93
  - Group Accident and Health Contracts, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L95
  - Group Annuity Contracts, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L96
  - Group Annuity Contracts, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L96.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 17)
  - Group Annuity Contracts, Samples, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L96.1a
  - Pension Trust Indentures, Samples, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L97
  - Pension Study Plan Summaries, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L97.1
  - Analysis of Pension Plans,Industrial Relations Counselers, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L97.2
  - Summaries of Pension Plans, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L97.3
  - Comparison Basic Steel Industry Pension Plans with Major Auto Pension Plans, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L97.B
  - Plans- Annuity, Social Security Program & Voluntary Employee Benefits Plan, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L98.1
  - Plans - Miscl., undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L98.2
  - Plans-Pension -Railroads, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L98.3a
  - Plans-Insurance Co. Group Rates, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L98.4
  - Plans for Guaranteed Wages, -Publications,Pamphlets, 1936-1956 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L98.5
  - Papers, undated (Box 18)
  - Plans-State Employees Retirement and Insurance, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L98.6
  - Health and Welfare Ins., undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L99.a
  - Health and Welfare Ins., undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L99.b
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Clark Amendment to The Soc. Sec. Act, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L115.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Clark Amendment to The Soc. Sec. Act, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L115.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: - Soc. Sec. Committee of the Social Science Research Council- Clark Amendment, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L116.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: - Soc. Sec. Committee of the Social Science Research Council- General, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L116.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: - Legislation- Bill and Amendments (H.R.12080)amendment, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L118
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Summary of Statement by A.J. Biemiller, A.F.L. C.I.O on Soc. Sec.(H.R.17550) Amendment, 1970 September 15 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L118A
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Welfare and Pension Plan Protection Act of 1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L119
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Social Insurance in Foriegn Countries, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L120
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -"Law and Contempory Problems" Duke University- Manuscripts of David F. Cavers and J. Douglass Brown, Articles on Old Age Insurance, 1936 April (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L122
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Robert Weil,Bureau Of Hearings and Appeals (H.E.W.),Concerning Administrative Conference of The U.S.-re; A study by Robt. G. Dixon, G.W.U,"The Social Security inability Program; A System in Crisis", 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L123
  - Papers, undated (Box 19)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -State Employment Compensation Laws, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L158.a
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -State Employment Compensation Laws, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L158.b
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Sixty Million Jobs,Henry A. Wallace, drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L159
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Correspondence, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L160.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Meetings and National Conference on Economic Security, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L160.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Publications and Releases, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L160.3
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Reports, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L160.4
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Unemployment Compensation-State Acts(suggested), undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L160.5
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Commitee on Economic Security- Tables-Miscl.-Memoranda, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L160.6
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Cost of Economic Security,Legislation Proposed in 1935,74th Congress, 1st Session (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L192
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation,74th Congress,lst Session, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L193.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: - Proposed Amendments,74th Congress, 2nd Session, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L193.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amendments,75th Congress, lst Session, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L193.3
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amendments,75th Congress, 2nd Session, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L193.4
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amendments,75th Congress, 3rd Session, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L193.5
  - Papers, undated (Box 20)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amends., 76th Congress, lst Session, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L193.6
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amends., 76th, 1st Session, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L193.7
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation, 76th Congress, 2nd & 3rd Sessions, Bills, Act, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L193.8
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Proposed Amends., 77th Congress, 1st & 2nd Sessions, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L193.9
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -78th Congress, lst Session, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: L193.10
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -78th Congress, 2nd Session, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L193.11
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -79th Congress, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L193.12
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -80th Congress, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L193.13
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -81st & 82nd Congress, 1949-1952 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L193.14
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -83rd Congress, 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L193.15
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -86th Congress, Act, 1959-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L193.16
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Legislation -Medicare, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L194
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: Medicine A.F.L C.I.O., Soc. Sec., undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L195
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: Medicine,"Intensifying Social Forces in American medicine"Lecture presented by Jerome Dollack,Soc. Sec. Dept. Ann Arbor, Mich., 1961 February (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L195.1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Old Material(Taken From Discarded Files), undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L200.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 21)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Proposed Amendments to Act, Memoranda and Tables, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L200.2
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Organization and Reorganization, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L200.3
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Organization Charts by Organization Units. Estimates of Appropriation, 1936 March 17 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L200.4
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Litigation, Briefs and Memoranda, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L200.8
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Registration of Insured Persons, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Bureau of Federal Old Age Benefits, Reports, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L200.13
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -William R. Wlllamson Memoranda,and other Memoranda of Actuaries, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L200.18
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Memorandas Prepared by M.W.L., undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L200.19
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Coverage of Federal Employees Under The Social Security Act, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L200.20
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Board Meeting Agenda and Memoranda, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L200.21
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Bureau of Research and Statistics, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L200.24
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -1936 Election Campaign, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L200.28
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Miscl. Memoranda and Correspondence, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L200.29
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Articles and Speeches, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L200.30
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L200.31
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Advisory Council On Soc. Sec., undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L200.33
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Miscl. Publications, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L200.36
  - SOCIAL SECURITY BOARD: -Bureau of Old Age and Survivers Insurance, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L200.37
  - Papers, undated (Box 22)
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Soc. Sec. Advisory Council, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L300
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Soc. Sec. Advisory Council Report on Cost Estimates & Financial Policy, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L300.A.
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -International Council Of Social Security Act and Staticians, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L300.A1
  - SOCIAL SECURITY: -Old Age Survivers Disability and Health 3 Insurance- Reports, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L300.A2
  - Labor Cases (Reproduced casesfrom committee clearing house and labor law reports), undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L304.A
  - General Subcommittee on Labor( Comm. on Education and Labor), undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L304.B
  - Workmens Compensation-Analysis by Chamber of Commerce of U.S., undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L311.2
  - Social Insurance Legislation, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L312
  - District of Columbia-Unemployment Compensation Legislation, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L314
  - Appropriations Legislation, 79th Conress, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L318
  - ASIAN AMERICAN FREE LABOR INSTITUTE, 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L319.a
  - ASIAN AMERICAN FREE LABOR INSTITUTE, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L319.b
  - Health Legislation, 79th Congress, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L321
  - Federal Employees Health Benefits, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L321.A
  - Health Legislation,Statement Concerning Hospital Costs, State of Mich. before Special Comm.to Study Hospital Costs by Maurice P. Shulte, United Steel Workers, 1969 November 12 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L321B
  - I.S. Falk Paper,"What Needs To Be Done To Strengthen The Voluntary System Of Health Care", undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: L321.C
  - Health Maintenance Organization, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L321.D
  - Prepaid Group Practice Plans, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L321.E
  - Papers, undated (Box 23)
  - Worcester Clinic, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L321.F
  - I.C.F. Incorporated, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L321.G
  - WAR MANPOWER COMMISSION: -Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L450
  - WAR MANPOWER COMMISSION: -Drafts, M.W.L., undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L450.1
  - WAR MANPOWER COMMISSION: -Reports and Bulletins, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L450.2
  - Washington Post Company (Includes The Evening Star, and The Health Progress Foundation of America), undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L451
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L457
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANYPACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Testimony and Transcript of M.W.L. before the Public Utilities Commission of California, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L458.5b
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANYPACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Miscl. Testimony and Exhibits before Public Utilities Commission of Cal., 1953 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L458.5c
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANYPACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Testimony and Transcript, M.W.L., Public Utilities Commission,Cal., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L458.5d
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Miscl. Transcripts, Public Utilities Commission,Cal., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANYPACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Miscl. Transcripts, Public Utilities Commission,Cal., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L458.5d2
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANYPACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Miscl. Transcripts, Public Utilities Commission,Cal., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: L458.5d3
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Public Utilities Letters, 1950-1954 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: L458.5e
  - Papers, undated (Box 24)
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: -Calculations, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L458.5f
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: -Calculations, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L458.5g
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: -Parabolic Salary Scale, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L458.5h
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: -Early Parabolic Salary Scale, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L458.Si
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE COMPANY PACIFIC TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE CO.: - Parabola; Commutations, Salary Scales Final Costs, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L458.5j
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE: -Washington, Public Utilities Commission Case, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L458.6
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE: - Oregon Legislation, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L458.7
  - AMERICAN TELEGRAPH AND TELEPHONE: -Management Reports, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L458.8
  - ALCAN: -Jamaica, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L461
  - ALCAN: -Jamaica, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L461.1
  - HUMAN RESOURCES DEVELOPEMENT INSTITUTE: -Miscl., undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L463.a
  - HUMAN RESOURCES DEVELOPEMENT INSTITUTE: -Staff Retirement Plans and Trust Agreement, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L463.h
  - Transport Workers Union of America, Local 234-Philadelphia, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L467
  - Papers, undated (Box 25)
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, Valuation-Tables and Summaries, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L467.1b
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1,Summaries of Data from Questionaires; Hand Tabulations, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L467.ld